<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-06-08T21:05:52+06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Daily Update on Bappy’s Existence</title><subtitle>Currently Existing @ Earth, Milky Way Galaxy, Local Group, Virgo Supercluster</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Why Have I Opened a Blog Site?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/06/04/Why-Have-I-Opened-A-Blog-Site.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Have I Opened a Blog Site?" /><published>2020-06-04T21:50:15+06:00</published><updated>2020-06-04T21:50:15+06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/06/04/Why-Have-I-Opened-A-Blog-Site</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/blog/2020/06/04/Why-Have-I-Opened-A-Blog-Site.html">&lt;p&gt;First of all, I am pretty bad at keeping journals(probably because I’m lazy). I write stuff in my journal for few days, then forget its existence for six months and rediscover that I have a journal. So, I thought writing a journal-like blog within the very device I study in everyday would be a good idea.&lt;br /&gt;
I have been working with Web App for quite sometime. I usually like to work with Node. But, I wanted to create a simple and personalized site. My friend Anirban’s site inspired me to create this. I decided to mess around with Ruby as a fun project. Jekyll seemed perfect for the job. It took a few hours to set up this static site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I plan to post rants, takes on movies and tv shows, update my new favourite music albums every month and finally keep track of everything new I learn.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zihad</name></author><summary type="html">First of all, I am pretty bad at keeping journals(probably because I’m lazy). I write stuff in my journal for few days, then forget its existence for six months and rediscover that I have a journal. So, I thought writing a journal-like blog within the very device I study in everyday would be a good idea. I have been working with Web App for quite sometime. I usually like to work with Node. But, I wanted to create a simple and personalized site. My friend Anirban’s site inspired me to create this. I decided to mess around with Ruby as a fun project. Jekyll seemed perfect for the job. It took a few hours to set up this static site.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My Fav Albums</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/My-Fav-Albums.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My Fav Albums" /><published>2020-06-04T00:00:00+06:00</published><updated>2020-06-04T00:00:00+06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/My-Fav-Albums</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/04/My-Fav-Albums.html"></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>